你怎么回来得这么早
What are you doing back so early?
栗宝忘了带钱包了吗
Did chestnut forget his wallet?
不是 我们看见不喜欢的那只猫
No, we saw that cat we don't like.
我试着用水瓶喷水吓唬它
I tried to spray it with a water bottle,
但它不屑一笑 我们只好落荒而逃
but it just laughed at us, so we ran.
你在外面干嘛
What are you doing out here?
享受美好时光啊
Enjoying the day.
即将到来的秋天 是我一年中最爱的时节
The coming of autumn is my favorite time of year.
我爱死落叶了
I love the leaves.
恶心死了 居然有避孕套
Oh, gross! A condom!
哇 我想秋天真的"来了"
Wow, I guess autumn really is coming.
谁会把这玩意从墙外扔进来
Who would throw that over our wall?
那只臭猫
That cat.
干嘛 他不但傲慢嚣张
What? He's not only arrogant,
还想让我们知道 他也有性生活
he wants us to know he has sex.
我只知道 如果我有九条命
All I know is, if I had nine lives,
我才不会戴套呢
I wouldn't wear a condom.
我们应该开始想想
Hey, you know, we should start figuring out
这个冬天怎么安置栗宝
what to do with chestnut this winter,
现在已经到了乱扔避孕套的高峰时节
now that it's already peak condom dropping season.
你说得对 栗宝是最重要的事情
You're right, chestnut is the most important thing.
但更重要的是 你觉得
But more importantly, what do you think
我为今天约会特意选择的毛衣如何啊
Of this vintage sweater I chose for my date with Andy?
还不错
It's nice.
但激情时 这衣服在计程车里难脱吧
But won't it be hard to pull off over your head in the cab?
我假设你们会在计程车里开搞
I'm assuming you'll do it in a cab.
麦克斯 我们才第一次约会 不合适吧
Max, it's a first date. That's not appropriate.
会吗
Is it?
我从来没跟穷人约过会
I mean, I've never dated poor.
初次约会那些事是可以接受的啊
What is acceptable on a first date?
我很优雅的 肛交吧
Well, I'm pretty classy, so anal?
我还没穷到那个地步
I'm not that poor.
你最好给他点甜头 留住他
Well, you better give him something to keep him interested
因为那家伙有一家糖果店
because he owns a candy store,
而老娘想一辈子都有免费糖果吃
and I want free candy forever.
他来了
There he is.
你能把他带到后院吗
Can you bring him out in the yard,
让他看到我穿着这身站在我的马旁
so he can see me in my sweater next to my horse?
没问题 怪人
Okay, freak.
不过下次有男人敲门找我
But next time a guy comes knocking for me,
你要把他带进我的卧室
you have to take him to my bedroom,
好让他看见我穿着杀手乐队t恤
so he can see me in my slayer shirt
躺在我塞满大麻的虫虫公仔旁边
next to my glo worm filled with pot.
你好 先生 我是来接您女儿的
Hello, sir, I'm here to pick up your daughter.
你要接她去干嘛
And what exactly are your intentions?
不知道
I don't know.
或许带她去来一次浪漫的夜游
Maybe take her on a romantic hayride,
然后用氯仿弄晕她
k'nock her out with chloroform,
拿她的肾脏卖钱买新iPad
and sell her kidney for a new iPad.
好小伙啊
Son!
来后院吧
Come outside.
钱宁小姐想让自己看起来像是
Miss Channing wants you to see her looking like the girl
因肤色过白 而被踢出白人购物目录的女模特
who got cut from the J.Crew catalog for being too white.
钱宁小姐 麦克斯 慢着
Miss Channing? Max, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
卡洛琳就是那个卡洛琳·钱宁吗
Caroline is Caroline Channing Caroline Channing?
对啊 她以前是个亿万千金
Yeah, she used to be a billionaire,
但现在她所有的钱都在这里
but now all her money is in here.
不对 里面有些是纽扣
Oh, wait, some of these are buttons.
好吧
Oh. Okay.
我还以为她只是一个普通的威廉斯堡姑娘
Yeah, I just thought she was a regular Williamsburg girl.
不 她还没这么堕落
No. She doesn't try that hard.
看来我低估了她
And I was wrong.
你好啊 刚没听到你敲门
Oh, hi. I didn't hear you knock.
你们俩好好玩
Well, you two have a good time.
年轻人 如果你不顺便从你的店
And, young man, if you don't swing by your store
给我带点精灵糖条
and bring me some pixie sticks,
下次就别想再见到我乖女儿
you'll never see my little girl again.
早想到了
Way ahead of you.
太棒了
Yes!
没错 绝对要肛交
Yeah, definitely anal.
小宝贝
Oh, baby.
瞧瞧是谁上班迟到了半小时
look who's a half hour late for work.
想必是跟糖果男约会得太火热哦
Must have been a pretty hot date with the candy man.
你有碰到他"那话儿"吗
So did you touch his whatchamacallit?
他有碰到你的"杏仁尖"吗
Did you bring him to almond joy?
他的黄油糖指就没接近过我的"投手丘"
His butterfingers got nowhere near my mounds.
我们可以像成年人说话了吗
Now, if we could be adults for a second--
你的"投手丘"更像是"锥子糖"
Well, your mounds are more like sno-caps,
不过继续说
but continue.
什么都没有发生
Well, nothing happened.
甚至在我连续四小时呼吸急促地说
Even after four hours of me breathing heavily and saying...
"我真的玩得很开心哦"
"I'm having a really good time"
我真的不想说这种话 但我觉得
Look, I don't want to be this girl, but I think--
他可能是同性恋
think he might be gay.
就因为你连续四小时的口臭攻势
He's gay because he's not turned on
没有挑逗成功 他就是同性恋吗
by four hours of coffee breath?
怎么了
What's up?
我真的玩得很开心哦
I'm having a really good time.
我得立刻去一趟洗手间了
I must go to the men's room right now.
那完全不代表什么
That proves nothing.
奥列格总是在找理由来"乱插"
Oleg is always looking for an excuse to put it somewhere.
不然我们也不用停止供应面包"圈"了
Why do you think we don't serve bagels anymore?
安迪不是同性恋
Andy is not gay.
我不会为了免费的糖果 就把你推入
And I'm not just setting you up for a life of confusing,
一辈子只有迷惑质疑 而无性生活的火坑
self-questioning non-sex for the free candy,
虽然很像我会干的事
although that does sound like me.
他真的对你很感兴趣
He is really into you.
他可能是对我感兴趣
He might be into me,
但他似乎对我完全不感"性趣"
but he doesn't seem to want to get into me.
或许他只想跟我做朋友
Maybe he just wants me as a friend.
不可能
No way.
等你再胖36公斤 并有羞于承认的可乐瘾
You are, like, 80 pounds and a coke addiction shy
你才有可能当上基佬的女性朋友
from being qualified to be a gay guy's female friend.
什么事这么重要 你们俩得像学生妹一样
What's so important you two have to be in here
在里面闲聊 而不去招呼客人
gabbing like schoolgirls when there are customers waiting?
如果你非要知道的话
If you must know,
我们在讨论一个朋友是不是同性恋
Caroline and I were discussing if someone we know is gay.
我在大学时有过一回同性恋的经验
I once had a homosexual experience in college.
跟小姑娘搞拉拉情吗
With another girl?
不 当时有个男生对我感兴趣
No, there was a boy who was interested in me.
他是足球队的队长
He was captain of the football team.
他会来我的宿舍
He would come to my dorm room
让我帮他写作业
and ask me to do his homework,
写完他就走了
and then he would leave.
算了 当我没说
Oh. Never mind.
我没有同性恋经验
I never had a homosexual experience.
阿憨呀 继续穿你的毛背心吧
Keep wearing those sweaters, Han.
有天他们会找上你的
It'll happen.
如果现在你觉得人生很悲剧
And if you think your life sucks now,
那刚才又加剧了
it just got worse.
瞧 新品种的嬉皮士
Look, a new hipster strain.
讽刺的阿米什人
Ironic Amish.
不行 我要亲自出马
No way. I'm taking care of
收拾这两个搅屎棍
these two butter churners right now.
我重复一遍我对某民谣摇滚乐队说的话
Look, I'm telling you what I told Mumford and Sons,
滚出去
Get out.
走啊
Go.
走啊 你们两个想装阿米什人的嬉皮士
Go, you hipster amish wannabes.
可我们真的是阿米什人啊
But we really are amish.
是啊 我们是来体验社会的
Yes, we're here on rumspringa.
而我是来耍点小酒疯的
And I'm here on a little bit of vodka.
我们体验社会就类似你们的"春假"
It's sort of like what you might call spring break.
我们可以脱离阿米什人的生活方式
We get to leave the ways of the Amish
来体现下现代世界的活法
and experience the modern world.
我恳请你们见谅
Well, I beggeth thy forgiveness.
有请两位客人上雅座稍候
Haveth a seat-eth in the booth-eth.
找个卡座坐吧
Have a seat in the booth.
厄尔 有两个阿米什人坐在我的卡座耶
Earl, I got two amish in my booth.
你得先跟他们声明
Well, you let them know right up front
结账不能用旅行支票和牲口
that we don't accept travelers checks or livestock.
你们是阿米什人啊
So Amish, huh?
是的 女士 来自宾夕法尼亚州
Yes, ma'am. From pennsylvania.
"女士"
"Ma'am"?
这称呼还蛮带劲的
You know what, that's kind of hot.
我总是觉得我得
I always thought I'd have to wait
再等个20年才能成为欲望主妇
20 more years to be a cougar,
但现在惊觉 我要变身了
but, rawr, here I am.
不如给你们俩上杯咖啡吧 我请客
Why don't I bring you boys some coffee, on me?
我们不能喝咖啡 女士
We can't drink coffee, ma'am.
咖啡是杯子里的魔鬼
Coffee is the devil in a cup.
我们想干嘛就干嘛 雅各布
We can do whatever we want, Jacob,
现在可是在纽约
we're in new york.
对啊 雅各布 你就听...
Yeah, Jacob. Listen to, uh--
-杰巴达亚 -真的假的
- Jebediah. - For real?
你看到她那对"奶瓶"有多大吗
Did you see the size of her nursers?
那俩家伙是真的阿米什人
Those guys are for real Amish.
我爱他们的文化
I love the amish culture.
你什么都文化都爱
You love every culture.
你连煎饼屋的旗帜都致敬呢
You salute the flags at IHOP when we walk by.
天啊 我想到了
Oh, my God. That's it.
麦克斯 问你个问题
Max, question.
阿米什人因什么而闻名
What are the Amish known for?
不是吧 重演小学六年级的桥段
Oh, no. It's sixth grade all over again.
就直接给我个"不及格"吧
Just give me an "F" and move on.
马棚 他们很会建造马棚
Barns. They build barns, and we--
而栗宝需要个马棚
We need a barn for chestnut.
跟我来 我负责讲话
Come on. And let me do the talking.
我非常擅长摆布小男孩
I am very good at manipulating young boys.
有次我给一个10岁的小孩当保姆
I once got a ten-year-old I was babysitting
我让他乖乖拿出零用钱 给我买了一盒甜点
to buy me a box of pop-tarts with his allowance.
这就是我们的公寓 地方不大
So this is our place. Not much, but--
你们有那么多东西
You have so many possessions.
-女士 你是不是有钱人 -是的
- Are you rich, ma'am? - Yes.
不得不说 那声"女士"
And I have to say, this "Ma'am" Thing
仍然让我心驰荡漾啊
is still working for me.
雅各布 别玩电灯了
Um, okay, Jacob. That's enough with the lights.
明天会有很多时间 可以好好体验电力
There will be plenty of time for fun with electricity tomorrow,
但现在很晚了
But it's late.
我们来安排怎么睡吧
Let's discuss sleeping arrangements.
你们俩在外面睡
You two can sleep out here,
我和麦克斯睡她的床
and Max and I will sleep in her bed.
-可以吗 -可以
- Does that work for you? - Okay.
抱歉 我忘了拿走我的胸罩了
Oh, sorry. I left my bra.
你的胸胸胸 罩
Your-your b-b-bra?
雅各布 别跟个小孩一样
Jacob, stop acting like a child.
我真替他脸红
I'm sorry about him.
大可不必
Don't be.
还好是她的胸罩
At least it was her bra.
如果是我的 那孩子早挂了
Mine would have killed the kid.
我想着明早可以开车
So I was thinking we could drive our truck
去我叔叔的贮木场
to my uncle's lumberyard in the morning
弄些木材回来做马棚
and get the wood for the barn.
好啊 不过似乎这里也有根"硬木"啊
Okay, but there seems to be plenty of wood right here.
注意点好吗
Oh, hello.
不要觉得丢人 雅各布
Don't be embarrassed, Jacob.
当你接触新鲜事物时 这是自然反应
It's perfectly natural when you're exposed to new things.
我第一次见到小摩托上的胖双胞胎照片时
The first time I saw a picture of those fat twins on scooters,
也性奋了好几天呢
I was hard for days.
你们俩何不出去跟栗宝玩
Why don't you two go outside and play with the horse?
好的
Okay.
谢谢你们让我们住在这里
And thank you for letting us stay at your place.
你们家酷毙了
Your home is dope.
你都不知道那个词是什么意思 杰巴达亚
You don't even know what that means, Jebediah.
嬉皮士就这么说 雅各布 超棒的
It's hipster talk, Jacob, and it's awesome.
你确定这是个好主意吗
Are we sure this is a good idea?
你也看见那小伙多性奋了
You saw how turned on he was.
他都在自己裤裆里"盖起"一间马棚了
He was practically raising a barn in his pants.
我们没事 他们也没事
We're fine, they're fine.
这是典型的男性反应
Just a typical male reaction
因为遇见像我们这样的性感熟女
to a couple of hot cougars like us.
如饥似渴 如狼似虎
Ra. Rawr.
你知道什么不是典型的男性反应吗
You know what isn't a typical male reaction?
不给自己喜欢的姑娘打电话和发短信
Not calling or texting a girl you're interested in.
何不你给安迪发短信呢
Well, why don't you just text Andy, then?
我应该发什么啊
What should I text?
"干嘛这么基 问号"
"Why so gay, question mark"?
我不知道
I don't know.
我唯一给男人发过的短信是
The only thing I've ever texted to a guy is,
"你身后有警察 别停下跟我说话"
"There's a cop behind you, walk past me."
就发个"好吗"得了
Just say "Hey."
好吧 发这个可以
Okay. I can do that.
"好吗"
"Hey."
手机都自动更正为"好基"了
Huh, it autocorrected to "Gay."
连我手机都感觉到了
Even the phone's getting that vibe.
好了 发出去了
There, sent it. "Hey."
我可以拿瓶啤酒喝吗
Do you think I could grab a beer?
-行啊 -不行
- Yes. - No.
人家免费帮我们盖马棚呢
Look, they're working for us for free.
一人拿一瓶吧
One beer each.
好棒 好棒 好棒
Awesome, awesome, awesome.
麦克斯 怎么能在咱家给未成年人酒喝啊
Max, you can't give underage kids beer in our home.
为啥不行 这不就是爱的真谛吗
Why? Isn't that what love is?
杰巴达亚 啤酒是魔鬼的口水
Jebediah, beer is the devil's saliva.
在威廉斯堡 邻居午夜过后还来敦亲睦邻啊
Neighbors come a-calling after midnight in Williamsburg?
这位威廉是谁啊
Where is this William?
我想当面夸赞他这堡
I'd like to compliment him on his burg.
姑娘们 我就下来想吃个小...
Hi, girls, I just came down for a cupcake--
等等 等等
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
稍等一下
Hold on.
你们厨房这两位可爱的小乖乖是谁啊
Who are the two cute puppies in the kitchen?
瞧你们俩
Look at you two.
真是这世上最可爱小东西了
You are the cutest little things.
就是 就是的哦
Yes, you are--
哎哟 这一个还勃起了呢
Ooh, and this one has an erection.
雅各布 别用肉眼直盯她
Jacob, don't look directly at her.
她就是巨乳版的日蚀 不可直视
She's like an eclipse with boobs.
抱歉 姑娘们
Sorry, girls.
我无意打断你们的"外送情人服务"
I didn't mean to interrupt your lovers' session.
苏菲 他们是来帮栗宝盖马棚的啦
Sophie, they're just here to build a barn for Chestnut.
我懂我懂 "眨眼眨眼"
Oh, sure. Wink, wink.
"盖马棚" 现在都用这个当代号吗
"Building a barn," Is that what we're calling it now?
"眨眼眨眼"
Wink, wink.
苏菲 卡洛琳说的是真话
Caroline's telling the truth, Sophie.
跟他们单纯是生意往来
It's strictly business.
原来是花钱招来的啊
Oh, so you're paying for them?
没问题
Okay. Ooh la la.
他们要多少钱
How much do they cost?
我也"想要间马棚"
Because, yeah, I also need a barn.
"眨眼眨眼"
Wink, wink.
苏菲 你要的小蛋糕 晚安啦
Well, here's your cupcake, Sophie. Good night.
但人家还想小乖乖玩会
Oh, but I want to play with the puppies.
时候不早
It's very late.
明早再来吧
You can come back in the morning.
这跟我村里圣诞节被取消时一样扫兴
This is like when they cancelled Christmas in my village.
你看 看他的裤子 那乖乖想我呢
Look, look at his pants. That one misses me.
晚安啦 小乖乖
Nighty night, puppies.
应该安迪回复了
That must be Andy.
颜文字 他用表情符号回我
Emojis? He sent me emojis?
他居然就用个破小符号回我
All I get back are tiny, little pictures,
亏我还花了精神跟时间打了个"好吗"呢
when I spent the time and energy to write "Hey"?
彩虹符 钱符 小松饼符 不算差了
Rainbow, dollar sign, muffin. Could be worse.
我有次收到 裸男符 裸女符 坟墓符呢
I once got naked guy, naked girl, tombstone.
我理解无能 但我赶紧去做了性病检查
I wasn't sure what it meant, but I immediately got tested.
小栗宝 你很快就能住得舒服安稳了
Yep, Chestnut, pretty soon you'll be safe and sound,
有屋顶帮你遮风挡雨
with a roof over your head,
我们再也不用担惊受怕
and you and I can finally be safe
不必再被那丢避孕套的臭猫精神折磨了
from the unending torment of that condom-throwing cat.
准备好要赴第二次约会了
All ready for my second date.
有骚货大驾光临
Slut, party of one.
你懂的
You know it.
而且 我还要带他去
Plus, I'm taking him to that bar
那家低档浪妹爱去求欢的酒吧
where only cheap girls go to get laid.
就是你爱去的那家酒吧啊
You know, the one you like.
那个"进去"吧吗
Oh, the Just Slip It Inn?
去那地方加我这身衣服
And if that place plus this outfit
他还继续三过我"门"而不"入"
doesn't put his pedal to my metal,
那肯定就没戏了
It's clearly never happening.
这衣服是挺性感 但也不是一看便知吧
Well, that outfit's sexy, but not foolproof.
还不够明显示意吗 跟我来
Oh, it's not? Follow me, please.
雅各布
Jacob.
我没说自己真那么诱人
And I'm not saying I'm that hot,
但我好歹没见过有人能
but I've never seen anybody drop wood
同时掉硬木又起"硬棒"的哦
and get wood at the same time.
宝贝再见 妈咪要在白天滚床单啦
Bye, baby, mama's going to get day-laid.
麦克斯
Hey, Max.
你介意我们脱掉上衣吗
Would it be okay if we take our shirts off?
-我们满身大汗又... -快
- We're sweating, and-- - Yes.
我是说 都好啦 随便
I mean, that's-sure, whatever.
你们决定吧
if you want to.
靠 我身上没小额纸钞[舞男小费]
Oh, crap. I don't have any ones.
能用喷水器喷我们身子吗
Could you spray me with that water bottle?
想得美呢 用这种伎俩
Oh, right. Oh, I'm going to spray you.
你们觉得这烂招现实吗
Is that really what you think is going to happen?
我洒水让你"湿身" 然后我看得欲火焚身
I'm going to spray you, and then I'm going to get turned on,
然后我也洒洒这匹结巴的小种马
and then I'll start spraying stutter stud over there,
最后一起玩3p吗
and then we're all having sex?
不用 麦克斯 我来
No, Max. I got him.
来吧 小乖乖
Here you go, puppies.
现在换打湿害羞的那个
Oh, now I wet the shy one.
小乖乖们 等会我也想请你们上来
Oh, and, boys, I'm going to need you to come up here next
我有东西坏了 来帮我修修吧
and fix something because it broke.
什么东西坏了
What's broken?
那个
That.
看我们后面那对情侣
Look at the couple behind us.
在这里就快全套 等会去厕所"搞"啥啊
I mean, save some for the men's room stall,
你说对吧
Am I right?
我真的玩得很开心
I'm having a really good time.
什么
What?
我真的玩得很开心
I'm having a really good time!
我去添点饮料吧
I think we need more drinks.
要来个杰克可乐吗[威士忌混可乐]
Would you like a Jack and Coke?
还是你想要个男人"杰克"
Or maybe just a Jack?
惨了 你会打来 肯定是约会不顺
Oh, no, if you're calling me, then the date's not going well.
我没发疯有幻觉吧
I'm not crazy, right?
是他主动找我 还求我跟他约会的吧
He did hunt me down and beg me to go out with him?
又没进展啊
Nothing again?
可能这地方撩不起他的欲火吧
Well, maybe he's not feeling that place.
全场就他坐怀不乱
Well, then he's the only one,
这里的气氛淫乱到我都想跟
'cause it's so horny here, I'm about to have sex
隔壁桌的红发情侣开搞了
with the couple at the next table,
逼得我都愿意跟红发男女乱搞了 真是超恶心
and they're both redheads, which is so gross.
等等 你们俩
Hold on a second. Um, hey, guys?
有事吗
Yeah?
很好 没事啦
Perfect, thanks.
那他干嘛还约我出去啊
I mean, why did he even ask me out again?
可能是因为我说了什...
Well, I kind of might have said s--
麦克斯 这下我更羞愧了
Max! Now I'm even more humiliated.
你居然逼个基佬跟我约会
You forced a gay guy to go out with me?
我是多烂啊 跟毕业舞会上的狼疮妹同等级吗
Who am I? The girl with lupus at the prom?
安迪不是同性恋
Andy is not gay.
我跟他相处时 从没听过他像基佬一样
He hasn't said one mean thing about strangers
对陌生人说刻薄的话
while I've been around him.
可能他是个靠着正常走路掩盖自己
Well, then he's paralyzed from the waist down
下半身不遂的男人吧
and hides it by walking.
我受够了 我要走了
Okay, that's it. I'm leaving.
别走 我来找你吧 可能有帮助哦
No, don't, I'll come there. Maybe it'll help.
我在你们身边的时候 你们俩总打得很火热
You two were really hot when I was standing between you.
也是 那你快来吧
True. Okay, and hurry.
我不想最后真跟红发情侣上搞上
I don't want to go home with the redheads.
酒吧干嘛放红发人进来啊
Why do they even let them in here?
现在离开对我也好
Leaving here is probably a good idea anyway.
我再待在这里 我怕我就要做一些
If I stay any longer, I'm going to do something
得"假装后悔"的"事情"了
I'll have to pretend to regret.
在我最爱的酒吧偶遇你们
How weird running into you guys here.
真是太巧了 我常无来由的就想来这呢
My favorite bar that I come to all the time just 'cause.
安迪 他们这是我们的朋友
Hi, Andy. These guys are our friends.
我们是阿米什人
We're Amish.
这乐团名不错
Awesome band name.
你带他们俩来干嘛
Why did you bring them?
我不敢把他们留在家里嘛
I was afraid to leave them home.
苏菲家都快没东西可以故意砸烂了
Sophie was running out of things to break in her apartment.
-你们想喝什么呢 -啤酒
- So what are you guys drinking? - Beer.
雅各布 敢乱说我劈死汝
Shut it, Jacob, or I will smite thee.
等等 我跟你一起去
Wait, uh, I'll go with you.
五分钟后没进展 我就跟红发情侣走
FYI, I'm leaving with the redheads In five minutes.
能给我们来一扎啤酒吗
Hi, can I get a pitcher of tap, please?
卡洛琳 你想一起跳舞吗
Would you like to dance, Caroline?
谢谢邀请 但我才不干那种事
Oh, thank you. But that is so not my thing.
而且 那里根本不算舞池
And besides, that's not so much a dance floor
是性病混合池吧
As an STD mosh pit.
好棒
Awesome.
她打给你了对吧
So she called you, right?
我看到她打电话 还配了一堆手势
I saw her talking on the phone using lots of hand gestures.
肯定是在说这约会糟透了吧
I figured it was about how bad the date is.
我尽量用文明点的词汇跟你说
Okay, I'm going to try and put this as politely as I can,
但你他娘的是猪啊
but what the hell is wrong with you?
对她下手啊
Make a move.
麦克斯 我真的很喜欢她 但...
Max, I really like her, but...
但是怎样
What is the but?
她可是卡洛琳·钱宁啊
But she's Caroline Channing.
你也是安迪·啥啥不是吗
And you're Andy something. So?
我就只是开间小糖果店的安迪·啥啥
Yeah, I'm Andy something who owns a small candy store,
而她算得上是公主了
And she was practically a princess.
那是以前 以前是公主
Was. Was a princess.
现在她穷得只剩五套内衣裤
Now she has five pairs of underwear
但她八天没洗衣服了
and hasn't done laundry in eight days.
我老实说 我用表情符号回复她
Max, honestly, I mean, I use those stupid emojis
是拖延时间 想好我想对她说的话
to buy time to figure out what I wanted to say.
表情符号作用就是在此
That's why emojis exist.
像我这样男人就不用亲口说出
So guys like me don't have to say,
"我配不上你 我是个卖口香糖的"
"I'm not good enough. I sell gum."
她就是你在店里遇到的那个女孩
She's the same girl you met in your candy store.
不 她不是
No, she's not.
当时她只是个普通的漂亮威廉斯堡女孩
That was just a regular, pretty Williamsburg girl.
现在她是文雅多金的卡洛琳·钱宁
Now, she's refined, rich Caroline Channing.
她觉得你多金又文雅
He thinks you're rich and refined.
-害他不知如何下"鸟" -什么
- It's a real boner blocker. - What?
他知道了你的真实身份 他吓着了
He found out who you were, and he's intimidated.
你得表现的廉价又粗俗
You have to act cheap and unrefined.
没别的招了
It's the only way.
来吧
Here we go.
我还帮你们点了脆饼吃
I also ordered you guys some nachos.
没放墨西哥辣椒
No jalapenos.
我知道那是魔鬼的调味料
I know that's the devil's garnish.
太好了 玉米脆饼
Great, nachos.
跟我一样廉价易得
They're so low-rent like me.
但我现在要先跟平常一样
But first, I'm going to chug some draft beer
大口灌点生啤
like I always do.
现在我要去骚女"乱舞"了
And now I'm gonna freak-dance.
骚货即将光临舞池
Slut, party of one
来吧 雅各布 姐要好好宠幸你
Come on, Jacob. I'm going to tear that ass up.
真的吗
Y-y-you are?
你看 她一点也不特别
See? That's not special at all.
天啊
Oh, my God!
快叫医护人员啊
Call the paramedics.
我让阿米什男孩爽死了
I danced an Amish boy to death.
雅各布好可怜 我好内疚
Look at poor Jacob. I feel awful.
人生首次"高潮"后的恐慌发作而已嘛
It was just panic attack coupled with his first orgasm.
医护人员说他会没事的
Paramedics said he'll be fine.
应该是这样吧
I think that's what they said.
他们边笑边说 听不太清楚
It was hard to hear over all their laughing.
安迪又回我符号了
More emojis from Andy.
圣诞树符 烟火符 马丁尼酒杯符
Christmas tree, fireworks, martini glass.
够了 我受不了了
Okay, that's it. I'm done.
他来啦
Well, here he comes.
你发这些是什么意思
What is this supposed to mean?
那些吗 就是这个意思
Oh, that? That means...
我爱死表情符号了
I love emojis.
看来我可以功成身退了
I think my work here is done.
麦克斯 我要进那台我们当初
Max, I'm going to go with Jacob in that thing
不愿意让其载走我奶奶的东西陪雅各布
we wouldn't let take our grandmother.
我来跟你道别
And I just wanted to say good-bye
并谢谢你对我们的一切
and thank you for everything.
你也帮我们盖了马棚
Well, you built us a barn,
我们差点害死你朋友 也算两不相欠啦
we almost killed your friend-I'd say we're even.
雅各布说他要回家了
Well, Jacob says he's going to go home,
但我在酒吧认识个女孩
but I met this girl in the bar
她室友昨天嗑药过量死了
whose roommate overdosed yesterday,
所以家里有间空房
so there's a spare room,
我打算去那里住
and I've decided to stay.
不错啊
Cool.
有什么人生箴言能传授给
So got any words of wisdom
我这个独自奋斗的小少年吗
for a kid trying to make it in the world?
没 你呢
No, do you?
记住 刚开始肯定会有不顺遂
Look, just know you're going to struggle for a while.
可能有陌生人假装问你时间
Someone's going to ask you what time it is,
当你低头看表时
and when you look at your watch,
他就把阴茎蹭你身上
he's going to put his penis on you.
但丹·萨维奇说过 明天会更好
But like Dan Savage says, it gets better.
虽然我的明天没更好
Although it hasn't for me,
那可能只对性向有疑问的青少年有效
so maybe that only applies to questioning teens.
总之 不必挂意不顺遂的人事物
In short, there's really no point to anything,
有时候 只要能吃上糖果或打上一炮
but sometimes, you get to eat candy or have sex,
不顺遂也就抛之脑后了
and that's when it all feels right.
惨了
Oh, no.
卡洛琳 那只臭猫
Caroline, the cat.
见色忘友 行
I'm on my own. Fine.
今晚别想吓唬我 死臭猫 别想
Oh, no, you bastard, not tonight.
今晚我奉陪到底
It is not going down tonight.
好吧 今晚让你赢
All right, you win this one.